https://www.myeasypics.com/privacy.php

EMAIL:
PASSWORD:
New Members Signup
OUR PRIVACY POLICY
FIRST AND FOREMOST:
MYEASYPICS.COM DOES NOT SHARE ANY OF YOUR INFORMATION WITH ANYONE unless we are requested to do so by law enforcement authorities.
WE DO NOT SELL or TRADE YOUR INFORMATION, EVER. Your confidentiality and trust is important to us!
WE DO NOT HAVE ACCESS TO YOUR FINANCIAL INFORMATION, EVER. All transactions are handled securely PayPal where you are protected and have full control over your subscription to our service.
WE WILL NEVER PUT YOU ON OUTSIDE MAILING LISTS, EVER. The only email you will receive are notices about your account, this site and the services we provide, and information that you request from us.
THOSE ARE OUR ETHICS AND WE STAND BY THEM - OUR CUSTOMERS AND THEIR PRIVACY ARE RESPECTED!
At times, MyEasyPics.com will collect certain personal information about customers and visitors to images hosted by us. Such information will include both identifiable personal data, as well as non-identifiable personal information. Identifiable personal information will be collected when you subscribe to our hosting services, or use our website for a transaction or subscription service. Non-identifiable information is gathered automatically when you visit our website or those images hosted by us, and stored for use in our system.
The purpose of this privacy policy is to explain to customers what types of information we will collect and how that information is used. In most cases, we collect this information to ensure network integrity and that we continue to provide you with the most relevant content and best possible service that suits your needs. In some cases, we are required by law to collect personal information about customers. Except where the law requires otherwise, we undertake to protect the confidentiality of such data.
Confidentiality
MyEasyPics.com respects customer privacy and the privacy of those accessing our website. We undertake to protect the confidentiality of our customers and users including all personal information supplied in the course of contracting with us for services.
We undertake not to sell your personal information to third parties for commercial or marketing purposes.
Collection of Personal Data
MyEasyPics.com collects personal data about our users when you visit our site; apply for a service; respond to a customer questionnaire; and through the use of cookie technology.
We may also combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from our business partners or affiliates.
A cookie is a data file that sits on your computer hardisk. The cookie is placed there by a remote web server that you have visited using a browser like Netscape or Internet Explorer. It is used to uniquely identify you during web interactions with a website and contains data parameters that allow the remote HTML server to keep a record of who you are, and what actions you take at the remote web site. You have the option to disable the cookie function in your browser, but will be restricted from accessing many sites as a result.
Use of Personal Data
MyEasyPics.com may on occasion use your personal information to contact and advise you of matters relevant to our hosting services, your hosting account, and in some cases to obtain your feedback. However, MyEasyPics.com does provide you with the ability to opt out of receiving any communications of this nature by contacting us and asking us ensure that you do not receive such information.
MyEasyPics.com may log your activities on our servers strictly to ensure the integrity of our network; collect IP addresses and information about your operating system and the type of browser you use for the purposes of network/system administration, and to audit the use of our site. This data however will not be used to identify individual users who will at all times remain anonymous.
Any information MyEasyPics.com collects from you through correspondence with us, whether via e-mail, telephonically or by written letter, will only be used to address the matters within that correspondence. If this requires referring such correspondence within MyEasyPics.com or to a third party to ensure customer service, your personal information will only be disclosed to the point necessary to address your query or concerns regarding your account with us, and will otherwise be kept confidential.
Public Space (Bulletin Boards, Chat Rooms and Third-Party Sites)
Any information that customers disclose in a public space, including on any bulletin board, chat room or any file MyEasyPics.com may host for you, is available to anyone else who visits that space. MyEasyPics.com cannot safeguard any information you disclose there.
Site Linking
MyEasyPics.com's website may contain links to sites that belong to third parties unrelated to us. MyEasyPics.com cannot be held responsible for any use of your personal information arising from you disclosing personal such information on third party sites. MyEasyPics.com cannot protect any information you may disclose on these sites and recommends that you review the privacy policy statements of those sites you visit.
Minors
MyEasyPics.com will not enter into a service subscription contract with a minor unless such minor has explicit written consent from a parent or guardian to do so. MyEasyPics.com undertakes not to contact minors without a parental consent .
Reservation of Rights
MyEasyPics.com reserves the right to disclose information about customers where required to do so by law or to exercise our legal rights or defend ourselves against legal claims.
MyEasyPics.com further reserves the right to share information with law enforcement to investigate or prevent illegal activities being committed over our network.
MyEasyPics.com reserves our rights to disclose your personal information where you have given us explicit legal written consent to do so.
MyEasyPics.com reserves the right to monitor user and network traffic for site security purposes and prevent any unauthorized attempts to tamper with our site or cause damage to our property.
MyEasyPics.com reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy or update it. This Agreement and MYEASYPICS.com's policies herein are subject to change by MYEASYPICS.com at any time, therefore it is important that you check this page frequently for changes. Customers and site visitors bear the responsibility to ensure that they have read the changes or updates as the case may be.
Budget Plan   2.95/mo.
50mb Disk Space
2000mb/month Bandwidth
No Branding On ImagesNo Branding On PagesCreate Image PortfoliosCreate Auction Galleries
< More Info
Bronze Plan   3.95/mo.
200mb Disk Space
8000mb/month Bandwidth
No Branding On ImagesOur Branding On Your PagesCreate Image PortfoliosCreate Auction Galleries
< More Info
Silver Plan   8.95/mo.
400mb Disk Space
20000mb/month Bandwidth
No Branding On ImagesOur Branding On Your PagesCreate Image PortfoliosCreate Auction Galleries
< More Info
Gold Plan   15.95/mo.
800mb Disk Space
50000mb/month Bandwidth
No Branding On ImagesOur Branding On Your PagesCreate Image PortfoliosCreate Auction Galleries
< More Info
SmartBand Plan   24.95/mo.
1200mb Disk Space
100000mb/month Bandwidth
No Branding On ImagesOur Branding On Your PagesCreate Image PortfoliosCreate Auction Galleries
< More Info
MegaBand Plan   39.95/mo.
2000mb Disk Space
250000mb/month Bandwidth
No Branding On ImagesOur Branding On Your PagesCreate Image PortfoliosCreate Auction Galleries
< More Info
::
SIGN UP© 2020 MyEasyPics.com Image Hosting SSL Secured All Rights Reserved
::
